SOFIYA KIRPACH

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

425-319-1043

SOFIYA.KIRPACH@GMAIL.COM

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Talented Graphic Design Intern proficient in Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop and InDesign with over one year of professional graphic design experience. Experienced in creating new designs with limited direction, as well as staying within brand guidelines. Enthusiastic individual accustomed to working in deadline-driven environments. Collaborative team player that works with others to maximize creativity and delivery. Well-developed verbal and written communication skills paired with excellent project management abilities.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphic Design Intern

Jan 2021 - Present

Heat Dance Company Los Angeles, CA

*Remote position

- Assist photographers and pro-actively participate in weekly team meetings with the owner
- Create high-quality social media content.
- Use Adobe Photoshop to edit photos and create Instagram video covers, Youtube Thumbnails and Youtube end cards.
- Design logos using Adobe Illustrator.

Brand Ambassador

Jul 2015 - Present

Independent Contractor

Seattle, WA

- Increase brand awareness through event marketing, demonstrations and brand promotion.
- Ensure all brand activation are executed to the brand standards by delivering professionalism, exceptional communication.
- Record and report consumer engagement.

Graphic Design Intern

Sep 2015 - May 2016

Trinity Lutheran College

Everett, WA

- Maintain a professional image of the college by ensuring brand consistency.
- Create posters and promotional material for events happening on campus and the community using Adobe Illustrator, InDesign and Photoshop.
- Work in a diverse cross-functional team of six people and meet project deadlines.
- Report to the main campus Graphic Designer.



SKILLS

- Adobe Indesign,
 Illustrator and
 Photoshop
- Mac proficient
- Detail oriented
- Typography and layout skills
- Collaborative and problem solving
- Strong attention to detail and desire for excellence

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts in Graphic Design

Trinity Lutheran College May 2016

Languages

Russian English

INTERESTS

Art

Hiking Traveling

WEBSITE

https:// sofiyakirpach7fd5. myportfolio.com/